FROM ME TO YOU
KURUMI
Um, by rumors, are you talking about the
ones that were going around about the two
- of you?
- Uh huh, those were some of them.
And does that include the one about how
I was the person who spread the rumors?
Yep, that too. -What about
people saying I'm a gang leader?
Gang leader?
A-According to what people were saying, I
had both of you acting as my backup... -...and
was supposedly using
Kazehaya to my advantage. -Huh?
Really?
Whoa!
That's honestly hilarious! What a huge
upgrade from you being a cursed ghost!
Can you imagine it?
Little gangster Sawako!
So annoying... These
girls get on my nerves!
Hang on... I feel like this doesn't make
much sense. If Kurumi was the one who
spread all the rumors about me...
Uh... for her to say I went through the
trouble of making you two my backup... but
then also badmouthed you...
...doesn't that seem a bit contradictory?
She obviously didn't think it through
beforehand. And if that's the case... then
it means that she's a complete idiot!
What? Oh no, please don't
say things like that about her...
She's doing so many horrible things that
she can't keep it all straight anymore.
Sure sounds like an idiot to me!
You keep saying "idiot this" and "idiot
that", but I don't even remember what
- we're talking about anymore!
- I'm just saying that she's obviously--
Stop calling me an idiot!
It's not even my fault! After all, I'm
not the only one who was spreading the
rumors, you know. The whole gang leader
thing was made up by the Kazehaya fanclub
and it caught on so fast that it
just blended in with everything else!
If it wasn't for that getting in the
way, then my plan would've been completely
- foolproof!
- Wait... What?! That isn't... uh true, is it?
Um... well... even though what you just said
seems to have caused a misunderstanding.
Maybe um you can try to
clear things up for us.
I think there's been a mistake
because I know you'd never--
Mistake?
There's no mistake.
I didn't care if I had to tell lies. The
bad rumors about those two and the one
saying you were the
person who started them...
...They were all spread by me.
- So, it was true then?
- Wait, she admitted it?!
Uh-huh. And if you were paying
attention, you would've noticed she did
- that earlier.
- But... But why?
You were in the way.
And to be honest, you still are.
My goal was to ruin the relationship
you had with Chizu and everyone else.
Then this whole time... Kurumi, did you...
...Actually hate me?
That's right. You really just noticed?
Yeah, we're friends, right?
I thought we were...
Despite what I said, I've
never considered us friends.
- Scumbag!
- See? This is the kind of person she is!
- Tell her how you feel, Sawako!
- Get her!
A-Are you okay?!
Uh, hey! Say something! Anything!
I can't take it anymore! This is driving
me nuts! Ugh, that's it! I'm gonna say
what's on my mind right
now! Is that okay, Yano-chin?
Kurumi!
This whole thing pisses me off, but what's
done is done, so I'll let it go. I don't
even want an apology from you.
Now... say what you will about me.
But don't you ever talk like you know
Yano-chin and Sawako again, you got that?
And this better be the last time
you make Sawako cry like this!
Hopefully that's the end of the
rumors problem., That's better
: Wow... I've never seen you like this
before. I wish I could be as bold as you,
- Chizu.
- Yoshida...
Also! Don't take
advantage of other people anymore!
Ugh! It's annoying! There! I
finally got that all off my chest
Uh, so much for you looking cool.
That figures...
Sawako. That's so unfair.
Huh?
Well what's so wrong with taking advantage
of people? I've had plenty of people use
me and once they get everything
they need, they toss me aside.
So why can't I treat
someone else the same way?
You've really got some
nerve, you know that?
Basically, you're saying you're not
gonna change the way you do things?
I mean, why would I bother changing
when there's really nothing in it for me?
Hmm... so that's how you feel.
You should probably know I'm not as
generous as Chizu is. That said... you don't
care even if Kazehaya
finds out about this?
Maybe I should go and
let him know right away.
Seriously?
- Yano, please wait--
- Go ahead, tell him!
What do I care? Just do it!
All right, then. If you insist.
- Chizu, it's time for volleyball.
- Oh, that's right.
Come on, Sawako, just
leave her there. Let's go.
Why're you still here?
Shouldn't you follow them
so you can all snitch on me?
Once you do, you'll have all
of Kazehaya's sympathy again.
Wait... Ch-Chizu! Ayane!
- Wow, she used my first name, huh?
- She did use first names earlier, y'know?
Please don't let him know.
Go ahead, tell him!
I'm not really sure why she would say
those things, but there's no way those are
- her true feelings.
- What do I care? Just do it!
I know for a fact that
isn't how she feels.
Please don't say anything
he doesn't need to know.
Well, to be honest, I don't actually
care if he finds out about it or not.
If you don't want me to say
anything, that's fine, but... you're sure?
I know...
...because there's no way you'd ever want
the person you like to think badly of you.
Uh... hey, Sawako.
I feel like I should probably say... sorry.
I didn't think you'd be so shocked by me
saying that. Although... it makes sense so I
should have expected it.
- I, uh... shouldn't have gone mother bear.
- What do you mean by "mother bear"?
Ayane... Seems like she was
really worried about me.
I... I should also be
apologizing here--I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me for getting
you both involved in all this!
Whoa! Sawako, we don't actually give a
crap about what all the rumors were saying
about us!
We were more concerned about what was
being said about you and if you were okay
- with it.
- If I'm being honest,
- I'm pretty used to it, so...
- Oh, I see.
Besides... when it comes to those rumors,
not everything that came from them was
bad.
I made friends 'cause of them.
Chizu and Ayane... I know that
they'll always be there for me...
That's why I can voice my feelings.
But then there's Kurumi
and I... Where do we stand?
- Damn it, we lost!!
- Not surprising considering we were
playing against members of the actual
volleyball team.
Don't be sad, Chizu...
I wonder where Kurumi is. I'm worried.
Same here. She didn't even make it
to the game, so I hope she's okay.
Well, maybe the reason we even won
today was because she wasn't around.
We got Mariko to sub for her
and she's actually athletic.
Forget being athletic,
Kurumi wasn't even motivated.
It's like, the very least you
could do is tie up all that hair first!
- Seriously!
Right?
Oh no... Did she not come
back after what happened?
She's too energetic...
Sawako Kuronuma, that's your name?
I mean my name is Sadako...
You're Sawako!
- It's perfectly fine...
- You've got this, Chizu! Just keep it up!
Get 'em!
Kurumi, she... called me by my real name.
She even called me her friend.
Despite what I said, I've
never considered us friends.
Regardless... she referred to me as her
friend that one time, and it was her who
talked to me first.
It may have been a lie...
but it made me happy.
I've never really opened up to anyone
about my feelings like this before.
Was that...
...A lie... or the truth?
Thanks so much for a good match!
- Hey, Sadako! Wasn't that a blast?
- I... had something I
needed to say to Kurumi.
What? Why?
- Huh?
- I'll be back, okay?
Oh, right. She didn't really say
anything back there, so it makes sense.
Come to think of it, it was only
us who said what we wanted, huh? Hm...
I haven't known her for very long...
And there are plenty of
things I don't know about her...
But... she did share her
inner most feelings with me.
So in return, I think it's only fair...
if I go ahead and tell her mine too.
My most precious feelings.
Something I've never told anyone before.
Oh? Is the girls
soccer game over already?
It's Kazehaya.
- You're only showing up just now?
- Ugh, jeez! It's only
because Pin gave me so much to do!
Huh? Oh right, you're on
the field day committee.
It's so hard being a lady-killer.
- What're you looking at?
- Hey, you think I should
even bother commenting on this?
Which part of it?
Don't tell me you
girls, too? Sorry, but no.
Huh?!
Where's Kuronuma?
She said she was
gonna go look for Kurumi.
Hm? Why? What's up?
Oh, you mean "that" girl.
- What do you mean "that girl"?
- It's exactly what it sounds like.
Being a stud really is a curse sometimes.
What a shame. She must be out
there, crying her eyes out somewhere...
- Huh?
While she's thinking of... me.
Ah, could it be that I've
broken yet another innocent heart?
Hey, you two better not fall for me like
that other girl did. You'd just be wasting
your time. 'Cause I'm
only interested in adults!
Pin! Cut it out, would
ya? Keep it to yourself!
Huh? What are you even talking about?
I mean, it's not like I've told everyone
yet! What do you take me for? I'm a true
- gentleman!
- You hear that?
It's hard to believe...
I think this is the first time I've
ever felt bad for the little troublemaker.
Yeah... even I
sympathize with her on this one.
I knew it. You've been
here since our talk earlier.
What? Did you come to laugh at me?
Was there another complaint you forgot?
Just spit it out then. Or is it that
you've come to pity me.
I wanted to tell you I like Kazehaya.
My feelings for him keep growing, so...
I guess I should say I love him.
Actually, that was what I came
to tell you in the first place.
It's something I've been
really wanting to share with you.
I've never said it out loud before.
I didn't know saying that to a
friend was gonna be this nerve-wracking.
My... heart's going a mile a minute...
But the fact that it's pounding makes me
realize that I really do like Kazehaya.
It's undeniable.
I'm assuming this is how you felt
when you shared your feelings with me.
I said I'm not your friend.
Remember? I don't want you
thinking our feelings are the sa--
I wanna know if you were nervous.
Maybe even a little embarrassed?
Were you overjoyed about it?
Like when you said it out loud or
when you realized you liked him?
"Overjoyed?" Why would I feel like that
after telling you? Get real... I told you
you're in my way!
I'll never forgive you for daring to
be around Kazehaya without earning it!
I had assumed with you,
I'd have no trouble winning.
Because nothing you do could
ever compare, since I... I've always...
It's true, she suits him so much
more than someone like me does.
I'll always... always like Kazehaya.
And I'm sure of that.
She likes him...
It's obvious. she really, really
likes Kazehaya, with all of her heart.
Kurumi, I hope that this doesn't sound
weird or anything but compared to when I
first met you, I truly think
you're much cuter now than you were.
I know I'm cute~ that's not the point!
But but what good is being cute?
If Kazehaya doesn't like
me back, it doesn't matter!
It just hurts...
...Because I know he doesn't feel the same
way about me as I do about him. Since
I've... always watched
over him, I can tell.
Why did you come back here anyway? I
can't believe I'm crying... with you
standing right in front of me like this.
I'm here because you know
Kazehaya's good sides. You said it
yourself.
So I thought, that you and I could
talk about them since we both like him.
I hate you... so much...
If I think about it,
the reason I envied her...
...Wasn't just because of something like the
way she looks or her aura, or because she
suits him better than me.
It's more likely that I thought the way
she was in love with Kazehaya, made her
extremely cute.
You saw me for exactly who I
am... and still do, even now.
Next time: "Rival"